Patricia Blasco

Cocoa, FL | (954)736-6242 | vilodye@gmail.com

Front-End Web Developer | UI/UX Designer

Creative and detail-oriented front-end web developer showcasing 3 years of experience using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and 1 year experience using React to build beautiful and functional user interfaces. Highly adaptable to work on any project, and quick to learn new skills and applications efficiently. Seeking full-time, part-time, and paid intern positions.

Skills & Abilities

- ✓ VS Code
- ✓ HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- ✓ React/Redux
- ✓ Node.js / NPM
- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ Sass
- ✓ Figma / Procreate

- ✓ Firebase
- ✓ Art & Design Experience
- ✓ Clear written and verbal communication
- ✓ Creative problem solver
- ✓ Fast & proficient learner
- ✓ Time-management skills

Education & Certifications

Nova High School - High School Diploma 2009

FreeCodeCamp - Responsive Web Design Certification - Jan 2021

<u>Udemy Certificates</u>

- Modern JavaScript (Complete guide, from Novice to Ninja) Aug 2021
- Zero to Mastery JavaScript: The Advanced Concepts Sept 2021
- Build Web Apps with React & Firebase
- Zero to Mastery Complete Web & Mobile Designer: UI/UX, Figma, + more

Work Experience

MARKETING ASSISTANT | MARMONT HILL INC. | 02/2019 - 02/2021

• Work from home position assisting VP of Sales with administrative duties using MS Word and Excel. Adopted a clear understanding of using macros and command scripting, and adapting to working with a variety of different back-end databases. Was depended on working quickly and efficiently, meeting weekly deadlines.

MARKETING ASSISTANT | OLIVER GAL ARTIST CO. | 02/2015 - 09/2017

 Assisted Marketing Team with establishing and deploying new artworks to retail websites. Responsible for creating product images using Photoshop, and frequently used MS Excel. Trained on site as a back-up graphic designer.

PROFESSIONAL PET STYLIST | FREELANCE | OCT 2012 - 2018

· Self-sufficient and professional pet stylist with a specialization for creative grooming. Established and maintained a loyal clientele of 100+ clients independently, and in a team setting with other groomers. Developed a strong work ethic and team building skills as well as client relationship skills.